happybidday.com 2016-05-04

# Welcome To HappyBidDay

**Privacy Policy**

**SCOPE**

HappyBidDay.com (hereinafter referred to as “HappyBidDay,” “Us,” or “We”) is a service provided by Razzle Enterprises, LLC.  (Hereinafter referred to as “Razzle Enterprises,” “Us,” or “We”.Razzle Enterprises provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of Happybidday.com. By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective 10 days after being posted on the website.

 **INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU**

You may visit our website at any time without providing your identity or revealing any personal information about yourself.  However if you visit our website we may use “cookies” or “web beacons” to collect and store your IP address, computer and connection information, traffic to and from our website, statistics on web page review.   
In order to actively participate in HappyBidDay.com, you are required com complete a registration form. We collect personal information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to survey, fill out a form or participate in an Auction. Once you provide us with your required personal information, you are no longer anonymous. In providing us with your personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of such information on our servers.  
In connection with your registration and use of our website we may collect and store the following personal information:

  * email address and physical contact information including but not limited to your name, address, date of birth and telephone number, password
  * all transactional information based on your activities at our website;
  * shipping, billing and other information relating to any purchase or shipping;
  * any correspondence sent to us;
  * financial information, such as your credit card information; and
  * other supplemental information from third parties.

 **HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

Any information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: ** **

  * to personalize your experience
  * resolve disputes, collect fees and troubleshoot problems
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms and Conditions;
  * customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising;
  * send you emails, inform you about our services, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers; from us and third parties.
  * compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties.
  * to administer a contest, promotion, survey or site feature
  * to process your transactions

 **DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES**

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of other, or protect anyone/s rights property or safety. We may also share your personal information with third parties who assist us in operating our website, conduct our business, or servicing you. Finally we may share information we collect from you with companies and organizations with whom we have a marketing or other agency relationship, generally to offer you goods and services you may have an interest in.

 **THIRD PARTY LINKS**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

 **CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION COMPLIANCE**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at any time by logging in and going to the 'My Account' page.

 **THE USE OF COOKIES AT OUR WEBSITE**

HappyBidday collects anonymous, non-personal information about your use of our site and your use of emails, special promotions and newsletters that we send to you. For example, we collect non-personal information about your use of our site and your use of the sites of selected sponsors and advertisers through the use of Cookies. Cookies are small computer files that are transferred to your computer's hard drive and result in information regarding how often someone visits a site and the activities they conduct while on that site (such as the chat rooms visited, whether orders for products have been submitted, etc.).

Every computer is assigned a different cookie by us. The information collected by cookies helps us dynamically generate advertising and content on web pages or in emails specifically designed for you and allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using our site and selected sponsors' and advertisers' sites, opening our emails, and for what purposes. We may use cookie information to target certain advertisements to your browser or to determine the popularity of certain content or advertisements.

Your browser software can be set to reject all cookies. Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject cookies in the "Help" section of the toolbar. If you reject our cookie, certain of the functions and conveniences of our site may not work properly but you do not have to accept our cookie in order to productively use our site. While it may be possible to link non-personal cookie information to Personal Information collected in other ways, we want you to know that if you accept our cookie we will not, without your consent, link the cookie information we collect to Personal Information you provide to us on our site.

 **WEB BEACONS**

We also may use Web Beacons to collect anonymous, non-personal information about your use of our web site and the sites of selected sponsors and advertisers, and your use of emails, special promotions and newsletters we send to you. Web beacons are tiny graphic image files imbedded in a web page or email that provide a presence os on our site.

 **DATA SECURITY**

Your membership and payment information (including credit card information) is secured using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology. We use this SSL technology to prevent such information from being intercepted and read as it is transmitted over the Internet. The encrypted data goes to a secure site where your information is stored on restricted-access computers located at restricted-access sites. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.   

Your account and the information contained therein are password protected. Please note that you are not permitted to provide your password to anyone else. We will never ask for your password in e-mails that you receive unexpectedly or that you did not request. Please remember to log out of your account and to close your internet browser window when you leave our website; this is especially important if you use a PC in public locations.

 **PROVIDING DATE WITHIN THE CORPORATE GROUP**

Happybidday.com is owned by Razzle Enterprises. You are consenting to allow your data to be provided within this corporate group. Security and confidentiality will be guaranteed with no change, and that the data will continue to be subject to the Data Protection Statement above. 

 **ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

 **TERMS AND CONDITIONS**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website. 

 **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY** ** **

We reserve the right to change or remove portions of our Privacy Policy at any time without prior notification.  Please check the website frequently to apprise yourself of any changes that may affect you.  The posting of any changes will be the only notice that you will receive regarding any such amendments or changes.This policy was last modified on November 9, 2010.
